[
    {
        "question": "We are born of one breath, one word",
        "answer": "Pneuma"
    },
    {
        "question": "I know the pieces fit 'cause I watched them fall away",
        "answer": "Schism"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cold silence has a tendency to atrophy any sense of compassion",
        "answer": "Schism"
    },
    {
        "question": "With my feet upon the ground, I lose myself between the sounds",
        "answer": "Lateralus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mention this to me, mention something, mention anything",
        "answer": "Disposition"
    },
    {
        "question": "Black then white are all I see in my infancy",
        "answer": "Lateralus"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have come curiously close to the end",
        "answer": "Reflection"
    },
    {
        "question": "Some say the end is near. Some say we'll see Armageddon soon.",
        "answer": "Ã†nema"
    },
    {
        "question": "I am too connected to you to slip away, to fade away",
        "answer": "H."
    },
    {
        "question": "Twirling 'round with this familiar parable",
        "answer": "Parabola"
    },
    {
        "question": "A groan of tedium escapes me, startling the fearful",
        "answer": "The patient"
    },
    {
        "question": "I embrace my desire to feel the rhythm, to feel connected",
        "answer": "Lateralus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Staring down the hole again",
        "answer": "Pushit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why can't we not be sober?",
        "answer": "Sober"
    },
    {
        "question": "Disembodied voices deepen my suspicious tendencies",
        "answer": "Culling Voices"
    },
    {
        "question": "Overwhelmed as one would be, placed in my position",
        "answer": "Rosetta Stoned"
    },
    {
        "question": "With my feet upon the ground, I move myself between the sounds",
        "answer": "Lateralus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dead as dead can be, my doctor tells me",
        "answer": "Ticks & Leeches"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wear the grudge like a crown of negativity",
        "answer": "The Grudge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Choices always were a problem for you",
        "answer": "Opiate"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have come curiously close to the end, though beneath my self-indulgent pitiful hole",
        "answer": "Reflection"
    },
    {
        "question": "So familiar and overwhelmingly warm",
        "answer": "Parabol"
    }
]
